jayisgames.com 2013-06-03

# Privacy Policy for CasualGameplay and Jayisgames.com - Walkthrough Guides, Reviews, Discussion, Hints and Tips at JayIsGames

CasualGameplay and Jayisgames.com ("CasualGameplay") takes matters concerning your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

## What this Privacy Policy Covers

  * This Privacy Policy covers CasualGameplay's treatment of personally identifiable information that CasualGameplay collects when you are on a CasualGameplay site, and when you use CasualGameplay games and services. This policy also covers CasualGameplay's treatment of any personally identifiable information that CasualGameplay's business partners share with CasualGameplay or that CasualGameplay may collect on a partner's site.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that CasualGameplay does not own or control, or to people that CasualGameplay does not employ or manage.
  * **Anonymous information** refers to data that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. For example, CasualGameplay collects some information each time a visitor comes to a CasualGameplay site so we can improve the overall quality of the visitor's online experience. CasualGameplay collects the visitor's IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type. CasualGameplay also collects data each time one of our products is used to access the Internet. CasualGameplay collects this user information for purposes of product monitoring, product improvement, and to aid future development decisions. This information may also be shared with advertisers and our business partners on an aggregate non-personal basis. You do not have to register a product with CasualGameplay before we can collect this anonymous information.
  * **Personally identifiable information** refers to data that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name and postal address, which may be collected in addition to the anonymous data described above. CasualGameplay collects personal information in the following ways from different parts of its Web sites and games: 
    * Purchasing a CasualGameplay game: CasualGameplay collects personally identifiable information when you purchase CasualGameplay games. The types of information that may be requested include your name, address, telephone number, email address, and credit card information.
    * When you register for a CasualGameplay account or newsletter: CasualGameplay collects your email address.
    * Other Registration: CasualGameplay may collect personal information when you register for other CasualGameplay services. CasualGameplay may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.
    * When you use our Tell a Friend feature: The e-mail address information you provide to us when you use the 'Tell a Friend feature' is used only to customize your greeting with your name and your recipient's name, and to deliver email notifications to you and your recipient. CasualGameplay will not share or sell this e-mail address information to any mailing lists.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * CasualGameplay will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
  * Unless you have agreed to recieve our newsletter, any names and email addresses you give us are NOT compiled into any type of mailing list, or otherwise used for any type of email solicitation. If you choose to receive these newsletters, but later decide you no longer want to receive them, you may request to be removed at any time by using the contact form.
  * CasualGameplay may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 
    * We have your consent to share the information;
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of CasualGameplay to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
    * We are required to disclose any or all information to the extent necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable laws, subpoenas, court orders, legal process served on CasualGameplay or in legal proceedings where CasualGameplay believes such information is relevant or believes in good faith that its disclosure is required by law.

## Cookies

  * CasualGameplay may set and access CasualGameplay cookies on your computer. CasualGameplay does not allow other companies to access the cookies we set on your computer. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to CasualGameplay's cookies.
  * CasualGameplay allows third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

## Security

  * In certain areas of our web site CasualGameplay uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
  * All in-game transmission of purchasing information including name, e-mail and credit card number and expiration uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. If SSL is not present or cannot be accessed within the game the option to purchase the product within the game is not accessible.
  * Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, CasualGameplay cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk.

## Other Web Sites; Links

  * Our web site contains links to other web sites. CasualGameplay is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * CasualGameplay reserves the right to amend this policy from time to time. Any amendments to this policy will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.

©2010, CasualGameplay
